couponbirds.com 2017-01-28

# CouponBirds Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect and use information when you interact with us. Your personal information is important to both you and CouponBirds. Please read the following notice carefully.

Information we collect

Personal Information is information that can be used to identify, locate, or contact an individual. We mainly collect your contact information, such as your name, email addresses, telephone numbers you provide to us. You personal information is collected when you leave your feedback, give us suggestions or report problems via email. Your privacy is very important to us. We mainly use the information to operate and improve our services. If you provide any personal information, we guarantee your information will never be sold or distributed.

Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of information that a web server sends to your browser that stores information about your account, your preferences, and your use of the Services. CouponBirds uses cookies to collect information about how our site is used by our visitors. With cookies, we can identify codes you’ve flagged as not working. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. If you don’t want to leave your cookies, you can turn off cookie collection within your own web browser at any time.

Third Party Services

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information by CouponBirds through your interaction with the Services. Other websites that may be accessible through links from our Services may have their own privacy statements and personal information collection, use, and disclosure policy. Merchants and business partners may have their own privacy statements, too. We encourage you to familiarize yourself with the privacy statements provided by these other parties prior to providing them with information or taking advantage of an offer or promotion.

Policy Change Notification

We may update this privacy policy to reflect new or different privacy practice from time to time. If we change any portion of our policy in the ongoing development of our web site, these changes will be posted at this page. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information about our privacy practices. Thus, you can use our service better at any time.

Children's Privacy

CouponBirds does not intend that any portion of the Services will be accessed or used by children under the age of eighteen, and such use is prohibited. The Services are designed and intended for adults. By using the Services, you represent that you are at least eighteen years old and understand that you must be at least eighteen years old in order to create an account and purchase the goods or services advertised through the Services. We will promptly delete information associated with any account for which we obtain actual knowledge that the registered user associated with the account is not at least eighteen years old.
